I'm not sure if I can do it, but I'll
try.
I'll try to do my best.
I'll do my best.
Hello everyone! We're back!
It's time for Tsutada Gamer's Club!
Yes, it's time!
The dumplings have arrived!
This time, we're going to start with the
game, but we're going to eat the
dumplings first.
Dumplings, pakupaku, yudon.
I'll start after I see the pinocchio.
Yes, it's a dumpling delivery.
Let's start with self-introduction.
Hello, everyone. I'm Runa Taniguchi, a
deco artist.
My favorite things are games, horse
racing, and anime.
Thank you.
I'm Kokubo Ino, the 14th member of
Shiritsu Ebishuaku.
My favorite thing is Gumi. Thank you.
I don't have a game, so I'll eat gyoza
first.
Let's go!
Have you ever eaten Osaka's Osho?
No, this is my first time eating Osho
gyoza.
I'm happy.
This is my first Osaka Osho gyoza.
It smells so good!
I've been craving gyoza for a while now.
I ordered gyoza in a hurry.
It looks so good.
It's crispy and fresh.
I can feel the heat.
It's warm.
Let's eat.
Do you like dipping gyoza in sauce?
I like it without sauce.
I thought you put it on the edge.
I put it on the edge.
I like it with sauce.
Let's eat.
Please give us a review.
It must be delicious.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's delicious!
Cute!
There's no chives in it.
There's no chives in it?
Vegetables?
Vegetables are also delicious.
It's delicious!
My first gyoza.
It smells really good.
I'll eat it.
It's so good.
It's so warm.
You are eating it while you are hungry.
I was hungry all the time.
While Inopi was typing, I was hungry.
delicious. There is no garlic. No, there
is garlic. It's delicious even if it's
not in it.
Do you make dumplings at home?
When Yuno's mother makes dumplings,
there is ginger. It's delicious with a
little ginger.
I'll eat it.
I eat dumplings without sauce.
I eat dumplings with ponzu.
It's refreshing and delicious.
I recommend it.
I enjoy the taste of the ingredients.
You are the best type.
I put a lot of sauce on it.
It's delicious.
I seasoned the meat and eat it without
seasoning.
Is there a lot of ginger?
I don't think so.
It's just the flavor.
It's definitely delicious.
I'll make dumplings next time.
I don't make much.
I'm a ponzu fan.
Ponzu is refreshing and delicious.
Vinegar and pepper?
It's delicious.
Let's try it.
Vinegar and pepper are definitely
delicious.
It's delicious.
Grilled meat goes well with lemon
pepper.
Is that so?
I'll try it next time.
There are many people who like to eat a
little.
There are many people.
There are people who like to eat
vinegar.
Lemon is absolutely delicious.
Lemon is good.
It's absolutely delicious.
My father and brother wear Gokkabouki.
My mother wears it too.
Only Yunopi?
Only Yunopi.
You don't wear it?
Yunopi is the type who enjoys the
material.
I see.
I think we'll do a game stream after
eating the dumplings.
I think so.
We're a gamers club, so we'll do a game
stream after eating the dumplings.
It's a game to eat dumplings.
It's good.
It's really good.
Gyoza makes me happy when I eat them.
It's delicious.
Do you go out to eat gyoza?
There's a member who likes gyoza.
Oh, really?
We eat gyoza at the tour's destination.
You take them to eat gyoza?
Yes.
That's nice.
Is there a gyoza shop called Utsunomiya?
Utsunomiya is good, too.
It's good.
It's great to have a member who likes
gyoza.
It's delicious.
The manager's house is in Tochigi.
When we had a concert in Tochigi,
the manager's mother brought a lot of
gyoza.
It was delicious.
I'm happy.
It's watermelon gyoza.
Here.
I got extra gyoza.
I feel like I'm eating a lot.
It's a big eating show.
I can eat forever.
I can eat gyoza forever.
It's really good.
I play games, too.
I'm into Gyoza.
250 people are watching this live.
You're not letting me play games.
I might finish it with Gyoza.
What are they eating? It's dinner time.
It's almost 7pm.
Are you eating gyoza?
Someone said they are eating gyoza.
If you haven't decided what to eat for
dinner, you might be eating gyoza.
It was beef bowl
I made pasta. I love pasta
Meat sauce looks delicious
Do you have any dumplings or pasta?
Dumplings?
Wait, I think dumplings and pasta are
delicious
I want to eat it
It looks delicious
What is the base?
I wonder what it is. Butter soy sauce.
Ah, it's definitely good with
pepperoncino.
It's definitely delicious.
I ate the first one. Thank you for the
meal.
I'm done eating too.
So, the second one.
Thank you for the meal.
Another kind of dumpling?
You can definitely eat both.
I can eat both.
Yes.
Both of us can eat both.
Let's try the next one. Is this spicy?
Thank you for the meal.
It has a little chili oil, but I don't
like spicy food.
You don't like it that much?
I think it's okay.
If you really don't like spicy food,
it's because of the chili oil.
If it's normal, it's not spicy.
The second one is to make it flow.
Let's eat.
We are big eaters.
We will eat another dumpling.
Dumplings are so delicious that we can
eat them forever.
I think I can eat 5 more.
It's delicious to put a little chili oil
in it.
It's refreshing.
It's a mester delivery.
I'm not good at opening this.
If I don't open it once, I can't open it
at all.
It's getting more and more crooked.
But it won't open for the rest of my
life.
I need 50 of these.
I can eat a lot.
This live stream is on the hashtag,
Stada Gamers Club.
Oh, that's right.
We're eating dumplings at Stada Gamers
Club.
We're eating dumplings. We're waiting
for your comments.
Like, it was a delicious dumpling.
Down there, left, right, which way?
Is it this way? Is it this way?
It's around here, so let's do it
together.
Please use the hashtag, Stada Gamers
Club.
What is Gamerz?
Gyoza
I'll play games after this
It's good
What are you eating?
I'll tweet it. Thank you.
It's like a gyoza club.
It's not that bad if you translate it
into English.
No.
I think it's important to eat well to
play games.
You're using your brain.
Yes, I'm using calories.
I have to eat well.
You are using calories, so you will lose
weight if you play games?
I think I will lose weight.
Will I lose weight?
I think I will lose weight if I play
games for a long time.
I think I will use my energy even if I
sit down.
You are too skinny, so I can trust you.
I can trust you.
You will lose weight if you play games.
It's a good diet.
It's a wonderful world where you can
lose weight just by playing games.
I want something sweet.
I agree.
Do you like sweet things?
I like soupy things more than sweet
things.
That's cool.
That was cool.
I also like fruits.
That's good. What's your favorite fruit?
I like Shine Muscat.
That's really good.
Shine Muscat is in season now.
It's really good.
I often get Shine Muscat as a gift at
live shows.
That's the best.
I'm the happiest.
Everyone, Shine Muscat is waiting for
you.
Yurupi will eat a lot.
Both of us play games so we are skinny.
Gamers might be skinny.
I agree. Many people who play e-sports
have a slim body.
But I think that full gamers are slim.
If you're thin, you'll lose weight if
you play games.
Will you lose weight?
I will.
It's a stream that stimulates my
appetite.
I'm getting hungry.
You forget to eat when you play games.
Oh, right.
When I'm concentrating on the game, I
forget to eat.
That's really true.
That might be true.
You eat four different kinds
2 kinds생
Amazing
This one
Tuna?
I've never heard of it.
Tuna Gyoza.
And this one.
Seafood.
The original is the most normal.
Seafood, tuna, beef.
Wait a minute. Tuna is definitely
delicious.
Unusual dumplings.
I've only eaten normal dumplings.
I eat a lot of chive dumplings.
It looks delicious.
Is it because the tuna is cooked?
Even if it's a tuna, it's a grilled
tuna.
I don't think it's raw. Seafood looks
delicious.
It looks like it has shrimp in it. It's
definitely delicious.
I'm told I'm full.
You can still eat more.
I can eat all of this.
How many pieces are in this? 5? 10?
5? 6?
6, 2, 12? 12!
I've already eaten 12.
It's good.
Close this one.
I'll use these two.
Thank you.
Do I put them on top of each other?
12.
I got 12.
Next.
I want a stand.
Thank you.
Wrap?
It looks so good. It's warm.
Everyone says, drink some drinks.
I'll drink.
It looks so good.
It smells so good.
The original seafood.
If you're going to eat it, you should
start with the original.
That's true.
The most normal one.
Is there another chopstick?
Thank you.
Wow, it looks so good.
Do you want to take it apart?
What shall we do? Shall we start with
Gansu?
Gansu...
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's pretty big.
Is there a volume?
The volume is pretty thick.
It was big before, but it's big on the
side.
The ingredients are amazing.
It smells good.
I'll have the good one first.
Enjoy the food.
It's full of chives.
It's a type of food with a lot of
vegetables.
It's delicious.
It's absolutely delicious.
I understand.
I'll eat it.
Thank you for watching.
It's delicious.
The ingredients are...
Oh, my God.
There are a lot of ingredients.
It's not the size of the 13th one.
It's delicious. I'm getting full.
As expected.
Wait, the lid might be leaking.
It's bad.
It's leaking from the lid.
I'll be fine if I put this on.
I'm satisfied with one.
Do you want to eat after this?
Yes.
I'm so full that I'm sleepy during the
game.
I'll eat tuna and beef later.
I'm eating 12 pieces before that.
13th piece is 15-16 pieces.
Yes.
I'm eating a lot.
It's like a game.
It says, are you playing a punishment
game?
No, we're not.
We were talking about eating dumplings,
and you prepared them for us.
We're giving you a reward.
We were going to play a game.
You made me eat dumplings.
It's a great project.
Thank you.
This is Gans, right?
Gans has shrimp in it.
I thought so.
It's delicious.
Is it a seafood?
It has a lot of ingredients.
It's really good.
It's not bad.
It looks good and tastes good.
Shrimp in Ganso.
It was shrimp.
What's in the seafood?
What is it?
Octopus and squid.
That's right.
It's seafood.
What are you going to do?
I'll do it later.
I'm full.
I'll eat seafood, tuna and beef after
this.
I'm full.
I ate 13 dumplings.
I'll take a break and play a game.
You ate dumplings at a great speed.
I ate them fast.
Shall we move?
Over there!
Let's move around twice.
The taste of happiness in my mouth.
It's delicious. It's always delicious.
The dumplings are still moving in my
mouth.
Wow! I feel like I've eaten a lot.
What should I do? I heard the sound of
my stomach being digested.
It's like a sound of a gurgling.
It might be a gurgling.
Let me put it on.
I'm going to eat it.
I just ate it.
You just ate it.
Shall we play?
Before that,
I'd like to say again.
This program is...
Yes.
Wait a minute.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
Is there anyone who wants to speak?
Ah, the sound is back.
I think it's because it wasn't on from
the start.
Where was it?
Ah, okay.
So, we're back to the game screen.
This program is made by the game fans of
Stardust Promotion
who want to do a show.
It's a program that is based on club
activities and is broadcasted offline.
Thank you for your support.
And, the hashtag is this.
Gamers Club.
Use this hashtag.
Please also tweet everyone. Yes, here it
is. Thank you.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting. I would
like to do APEX.
Alright. I've had a good meal.
I'm full.
I want to do it.
I ate a lot. I ate a lot.
I made a mistake. My stomach is a
dumpling.
I'm happy with dumplings in my mouth.
Yes, do you want to do it with Dio?
Then I would like to do it with Dio at
first.
Start.
Good.
The new season has started, right?
Yes, it's really recent.
The new season has started.
It's been a while since I've done a live
stream.
It's been a month since I did a live
Have you been doing it recently?
I haven't done it yet.
I'm looking forward to the live stream.
I haven't done it much lately.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to enjoy it.
I'm going to do my best in the race from
here.
Yes, please.
I want to go to Octavia.
My favorite weapon is Kirby.
I found Kirby.
My favorite enemy is Nemesis.
I burned it to my head.
I'm going to do my best.
Hip
YO swordsman Yes pah this I like to go
this up
me
Where do you like to go?
I usually go to the square place.
But I'm defeated soon.
Is it here?
It was the other side.
But I'm defeated soon.
Oh, I see.
There are many big squares.
But there is no enemy, right?
No, I'm here.
I'm going to the other side.
I should be closer to the enemy.
I'm close.
You can go there.
Thank you.
I found a paper.
I'm fighting over there.
I was defeated.
Hey!
Really!
I hit 110.
There were two of them.
Damn it.
What a place to open.
What?
Please stop.
Come on.
Let's go again.
It's hard to fight back.
Fight back.
No, this is...
Two people are no good.
Don't do it.
I should have run away.
That place is...
I mean, that place is...
It's a place called Estate, but...
It's a popular place.
I mean, it's a popular place.
It's popular depending on the place.
It's a place where you can get off with
a guaranteed one-power.
I agree.
If you're lost, you'll go there.
Yeah.
Wow, Octane's fingers are so realistic.
Yes.
Wow, even the wrinkles on his fingers
and nails are reproduced.
He is cool.
Octane is cool.
He is getting stronger.
He fights hard in such a place and his
fighting power gets stronger.
I see.
So...
I will aim to be a champion in every
fight.
Yes.
I think I was pretty good in the first
fight.
Wow.
I don't think I'm good this time.
What?
I don't think there is anyone.
Yay! I can do whatever I want.
There is no one this time.
Oh.
I can do whatever I want.
Yay!
If there wasn't a
I'm going to enter this room.
Yes.
Hmm, what should I do?
I think I can choose slowly.
Should I take one?
It's okay to play slowly.
Because there are no enemies.
If there is a weapon I like, I will use
it.
Okay.
I heard something.
There it is.
Cut it out.
I got a backpack.
Purple?
Purple is the best.
It's hard to guess.
I'm glad.
Nice.
I'll bring a charge rifle.
Charge rifle.
I'm glad.
I'll bring a charge rifle.
It would be great if we could all get
Charley Nemesis.
OK.
Nemesis, right?
Leave it to me. I'll do my best to find
it.
I found the carbine.
I found the carbine, but I'll use it.
The carbine I got from the next person
has more power.
I'll change it.
Then, is there a Nemesis or a
Charmander?
There is a Charmander.
Oh, a sniper.
Oh, I found a sniper scope.
I'll go with Nemesis.
Haboku.
It's a good start.
Nice.
Be ready.
Jump while landing on a wall in this
corner.
It was a perfect change.
It's painful...
I'll give you a perfect theme.
I'll just run...
Thank you.
Um... Volt, it's got several uses,
Triple Take and hell本...
Volt is pretty strong, too.
Thank you.
Oh, you can take both of them up?
I think it's good
It's good, right?
It's a good feeling
I see.
I didn't eat any food, so I'm being
attacked.
I agree. The enemies don't come to us.
They don't come to us.
But...
The enemies are in the safe zone, so
they might come to us.
They might come from outside.
They are coming.
What?
They are coming to the inner area.
I see.
he's coming
lets hold the door
aronminute
I'm charging the shield.
I'm using the same armor.
I see.
Which way are you coming from?
I'm going to the house in the middle.
I see.
I found the enemy.
It's quite far away.
Welcome.
If I show my face, I'll definitely be
killed.
I'm on the upper floor.
It's quite close.
I can see you from here.
There he is.
Oh, I'm going to win.
I can't hit him.
pika pika
the one that were looking for
I think I saw him
He's coming this way
The old man is on the left
The house on the right
Where did he go?
He jumped and flew away
Where is he?
He's on the roof
I'm going to shoot him
The house next to the house
The one on the other side.
Oh, let's open the door.
Ouch!
Hey! Stop it!
The enemy is coming.
Ouch!
I'm going to die.
I did it.
My knockdown shield is purple, so it's
strong.
I should have been protected by the
knockdown shield of the hero P!
No, this is the enemy's fault.
The enemy was strong.
The voice of the hero P, who was like an
angel, was heard from the side.
I've packed it properly.
I've put in the armor.
I'm going to lose weight.
That's right. You're going to lose
weight.
I'm going to lose weight.
I've already digested the dumplings.
The dumplings are already digested.
The enemy is strong.
How should I move when I'm in that
position?
In games like Apex, it's better to shoot
from above than from below.
So if you shoot from above, you can
shoot from above.
If you shoot from below, you can shoot
from above.
It's easier to hit the head.
That's right.
So it's better to shoot from above.
It's better to shoot from above.
I'll try to use it.
And use the shield.
It's important to shoot from a building
or something.
I see.
I've got it.
I think this is the place I go often.
Where is it?
Oh, it's not. But I like this place too.
It's close.
There are stairs and ropes to go down.
I know! I know! It's a big place.
Is the enemy coming here?
No, I'm... No, I'm kidding.
I went deep.
I went deep, so it's okay.
This way is the end.
I'm going to the enemy.
It's a little far away, but it's
fighting.
Send it over here too.
I saw her again!
Oh yeah, how was Char-Lighter? It was
different.
Char-Lighter is that thing that moves
like a beam.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Before it was a beam, but this time it's
like a boing!
It changed?
It changed to a shape I'm not good at.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Before it was like a
long beam.
It's changed since the new season.
Char-Rai was too strong.
Yeah, it was pretty strong.
It was a bone after it was stored.
It's become very hard to use.
I can't do it like before.
If I could hit the last one, it would
have been difficult.
I think it's difficult.
I think I'll rely on Sentinel from now
on.
That's right!
We used Sentinel before, right?
Yes, yes.
At that time, Yunopy was really strong.
I want you to look at the archive.
The last time, Eppe.
The last time.
If you haven't seen the last Eppe's
stream, please look at it.
Yunopy was really good at Sentinel.
The team was saved.
Wow.
She was strong at the same time.
By the way, Yunopy was screaming that
she was strong.
It was probably the last battle.
Yes, yes.
I think it was when we won the champion.
That's right.
She was really strong.
If you haven't seen it, please do.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You can see a cool Yuno-P.
Oh, it's me.
Oh, it's true.
Hey, wait.
No, it's not!
I forgot that I can make Nemesis now.
Oh, really?
So, I can make it with this.
I can make it with 30 yen.
I'll make it.
I forgot.
I'll throw this away.
I can make it now.
This time the faith occasion happened to
make a return.
Did you score 3 or 4 kills?
Oh, I should craft it.
Jump tower.
Yes, I have a jump tower.
But, there is a new Anji with me.
There is a new Anji.
There is Nemesis.
There is?
Nice.
With this, I finally got the Nemesis I
wanted.
The Nemesis you wanted.
It's a big name.
Nice!
Yay!
I'm going to make an egg.
Oh, good idea.
Thank you.
I don't have any.
Hey, there are bad guys over there!
I don't see them.
If you find a scope for snipers, please
let me know.
OK, OK, OK.
Then, let's go to another place.
OK.
Here...
Pathfinder's White Knight.
Oh!
I found a scope.
Oh, thank you.
Do you have a rock vial?
I'm totally fine.
OK.
Thank you.
Oh, it's strong.
I'm not sure.
There are no enemies.
There is a death box.
I can use the NEO.
Let's go there.
I can go there.
What should I do?
Oh! There's a 480 sniper too!
Oh, what should I do?
There's everything.
Yes, please use whatever you like.
I'll go with the easiest one.
The 480 is pretty popular.
It depends on the person.
Nemesis?
Yes, Nemesis.
It has a gold extension energy magnet.
Oh!
I got it.
I can attach it to Nemesis.
Wow, Nemesis is running.
He is saying run.
lol
I like this place.
This place is nice.
It's fun.
If I reload,
I think I'll get more bullets.
Oh, I found a better one.
Did you get it?
I got it.
If you open Nemesis and reload,
you can get more bullets.
you can see the number of bullets.
Yes, there are 32 bullets.
Wow, that's great.
Thank you.
Scalpia...
1 minute left. The ring is not far away.
Sniper?
Yes
Sniper
Oh
I think it's better to have it.
Purple is the best color to wear.
It's good after gold.
I put it on.
Thank you.
Then, let's go to the safe zone.
This is not safe zone.
There are too few enemies.
Yes.
I hear a car.
Is there someone behind?
No.
I think someone is coming.
There is someone.
I was hit.
I was hit by a car.
If you hit a car, it will damage two
people.
Wow!
If you hit a car, it will damage two
people.
It's strong.
It's good.
There is an armor.
I found a body shield.
I got it.
Thank you.
Nice.
I did it.
Do you have anything else you want?
Do you eat?
I'm eating.
OK.
I'm not feeling like eating.
I'm done.
Let's stay here for now.
Let's move to the next place.
OK.
Where are we going?
I'm not feeling like eating.
Round 3, start the ring countdown.
It's more fun over there.
Which way should we go?
Let's go this way.
There's no enemy at all.
Right? I mean, look at the number of
units.
Eight.
There are eight units.
That's not much.
It's eight.
It's fast.
Oh!
I hope I can get into the safe zone.
Oh, they're fighting.
Already.
There's no safe zone.
I'm in the safe zone for now, but I
think the final safe zone is in the
estate.
Estate?
I'm going to the other side. I'm bored
here.
Really? I hear a lot of enemies.
There are a lot of enemies.
I don't know. I think I was killed by
the enemy.
There's a lot of enemies.
There's a squad.
I'll stay here for now.
I'll go to the other side.
Certainly.
I'll take this area.
I'll go into the safe zone.
If the enemy is behind me, I'll lose.
So I should take care of the enemies who
are trying to enter the safe zone.
I'll take care of the enemies behind me.
If there's no one behind me, I don't
have to worry about the enemies behind
me.
I see.
Then I can focus on the enemies in front
of me.
Thank you for watching.
No one's running towards me.
I don't think anyone's here.
If no one's here, I'm lucky.
6 squads left.
Report.
A new kill leader has been found.
Oh!
5 squads?
There's no one behind me.
I wonder why there are 5 squads.
There might be a lot of them.
What should I do?
This way?
I'm so worried.
It's a peaceful time.
I'm so bored.
It's true. We're fighting each other
here.
We should go over there.
Enemy spotted.
It would be strong if we could get on
top of this.
But I think there are some vanguards.
What should we do?
Let's defeat the enemies above.
Save, save, save, save.
Thank goodness.
We're disappearing into the sky.
I'll put on a cover.
We're going to die.
We can make it.
Let's go.
Maybe there are enemies.
I can't see any of them.
They are down there.
I can see them.
I found the enemy.
They are far away.
They are small like cockroaches.
They are down there.
They are attacking.
34.
What is that?
That's quite...
There he is.
Ah, that person is about to die.
He's going to die.
Is he going to die?
He's going to be defeated.
He's going to be defeated. OK.
For now, I think I'll stay up here.
OK.
I'll stay up here.
I think he's going straight down.
He's not going this way.
There's a lot of people running around.
It's hard to get here.
It's close.
I'll check the inside of the house.
Thank you.
There are 4 more teams.
Oh!
I'll take this.
I made a mistake.
What?
I should crouch.
I think you can be a champion.
Oh?
I think I can punch it.
It's in here.
What's in here?
Here.
It's close.
Oh no, I slipped.
If I shoot from this angle,
I'll get hit, so if I move back a
little...
Stay away from the danger.
Someone might be aiming at me.
If it's really dangerous, I'll go this
way.
There's a wall here.
It's safe here, so I won't go.
I can only shoot from this side.
If it's dangerous, I'll stay here.
The race said to stay away from the
danger.
Maybe...
Maybe they are aiming at me.
If they see me, they will attack me.
The race is passive.
It's an original ability.
If they see me,
they will stay away from the danger.
They will announce me.
They will announce you.
I can't find it.
The one who was in the previous place is
away from the danger.
OK.
I'm going to go.
If we can get the top, we can take it.
Isn't it like the bottom?
I think there are a lot of enemies.
I think we have to shoot them from
above.
If we take this, we can get the top.
I think there are enemies here.
I think they are going to wake up.
But there are another team.
So we don't have to go down.
It's strong.
I think it's going to hit me.
That's why it's dangerous to go down.
Maybe it was aiming at me from below.
It might come out from here.
I think I should look over there.
It's in the house.
It's in the house. It's in the house.
It's being shot.
It's coming from below.
I think I should check here.
Around here.
I can get a good angle from here.
I think I can go around there.
I'll recharge my shield.
And then I'll shoot from above.
It depends on the next anti-air, but I
don't think I'll do it.
It's the last one.
I'll go to the tsunami here.
I saw something hanging in the house.
I'm in the house.
I can't go to the angle.
I think I can go here.
They're shooting.
Yeah.
I'm going to drop here.
You're going to drop here?
I was surprised when I jumped.
Yeah, yeah.
If you drop, you'll die.
Be careful.
You'll be killed.
Okay.
I'm going to shoot.
Up there.
What is this? I want to shoot.
It hurts.
OK.
Zenopi, can you do it?
Thank you.
This is strong.
Zenopi is doing this.
This is a gun.
I see.
This is strong.
They stay stuck here until it wears out.
Wait, I don't want to give up.
If you drop it, you can roll it.
You can roll it a little back.
Just be careful of the anti-air.
I'll use the Phoenix kit.
It's an anti-air.
I'll leave it here.
Do your best.
Did I get shot?
Thank you for watching.
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
I'm second.
But Nina is amazing.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't take you to the champion.
No, not at all.
You're second.
Seriously, the knockdown shield from
Yunopy is really helpful.
There was no cover.
There's no place to hide.
If you use the knockdown shield, you can
hide.
That's good.
That's pretty strong.
It's really helpful when you're in the
shield.
I'm glad.
It's the strongest technique.
Yes.
It's been a while since I had so much
fun.
Oh, I leveled up.
Nice!
I'm at 20!
I can do it at 30.
Nice, nice.
It was fun.
It's time for gyoza.
Gyoza, gyoza!
Is it time for gyoza?
Let's do it again.
Oh, yay!
Okay, last one.
One more!
Okay, so we're going to do the last one
in a trio?
That's right.
Okay, then.
Let's increase our team.
Let's replenish our team.
I'd like to go.
Okay.
Let's go. Last one.
Let's go.
So, the fans who are watching right now,
there's a chance that they'll join us.
The fans...
There's a chance that they'll join us.
Thank you.
By the way, I just started this, but I'm
already in second place.
That's right. It's Gyoza power.
Gyoza power!
Oh, Pathfinder.
Pathfinder...
He's strong.
He's using his passive a lot.
That's true.
Can I use the good job?
When this is over?
The good job.
It looks strong.
The enemy might be strong too.
Is it in the voice chat?
Can you hear me?
No, I don't think it's in the voice
chat.
It's not marked on the VCR.
Yuno's mic is blinking.
Oh, it's true.
Can you hear me?
I can't hear you, so it's fine.
Okay, let's go.
I'm here.
I don't think there's anyone this time.
Please play as much as you like.
I'm going to get into the biggest house.
Please get in.
Have a water
Streaming System It's quite early
About the wind
Oh, we meet again
Oh, purple came
Eh, too strong
Nice
But purple doesn't have a backpack
Nemesis is really strong, so there are a
lot of people using it
I feel like everyone is using it
Even if I could hear it, I couldn't hear
it.
Can't you hear it?
It's okay. I just think this person is
talking.
I can't hear it.
Nice. Why can't I hear it?
I wonder why.
This person is also...
I think that this person is talking to
herself.
She's talking to herself.
She said, she likes Nemesis.
Yeah, she's appealing to her.
Yeah, she might get Nemesis.
She might like Nemesis.
I'd be happy if she gave me Nemesis.
Nemesis is going to make it.
Yes, I'll make it.
Oh, I found a purple armor.
Okay, I got the purple one.
I got it for you.
I got Nemesis.
Yay! Thank you.
Thank you.
Cute.
Jump.
Thank you.
I'm the champion.
You're the champion.
I have no time tocertainment
I had a win
Yes, I found it.
I see.
There's a care package.
Oh, it's a plower.
Isn't it a backpack?
Can you make a backpack?
I can make a backpack.
How much is it?
Wait a minute.
75 yen.
How much do you have now?
I have 100 yen.
Then I can make it.
I can make a purple backpack.
Yay! Let's make it.
Okay, I'll make it and wait.
I'm crafting.
Really.
Wait a minute.
I'm glad that I can deliver it to the
house at any time.
I'm a student because I don't have any
other radio today, so I can do it until
about 22 o'clock.
I'm getting attacked.
I'm a student because I don't have any
other radio today, so I can do it until
about 22 o'clock.
16 years old.
16 years old?
Oh no!
Again!
Oh yeah, everyone's 16 years old.
It's dangerous, so we have to go home.
Let's get the champion.
Oh yeah, until 10 o'clock.
Yeah.
Enemies!
They're shooting over there.
I'll bring the champion.
There's a lot of enemies jumping.
Hey, Mire.
Hey!
Ah, this is it.
Oh, nice!
Ah, I ran out of scopes.
Ah.
I see.
When you have a longbow, it's a bit...
It's good.
It's good but...
I can't hit anything.
The enemy is coming.
It's close but...
Let's go find the scope.
Yeah.
Let's go find it.
Self-recovery.
I saw it the other day.
Eno is small
Heavy
Where are they?
Oh! Oh!
Scope!
Found it!
Ah, I messed up
Ah, this is bad, my teammates are...
This is bad
My teammates...
I'll go.
I'll ignore them.
I think they'll come after me.
Stop it.
Where are you?
I'm sorry.
I'm charging my shield.
Roll slowly.
Let's go.
Fufufu
Good, let's go
Yes, ah!
I could collect armor
No, it's fine
Not far?
Well, it's fine
Everyone lost their armor
Any kriefers here?
Yes!
Nice
You'll gather kriefers again while
running
Yee
Haha
I'm...
feeling that you're turned
back
Ah
mural
It's perfect.
Nice!
Ah, I'm being shot again.
Can you stop that?
I'm just rolling around.
I think I can jump on that.
The one that the boss gives me.
Where should I jump?
Maybe in the safe zone?
I should try this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, that way.
Nice, nice, you're good!
The bottom side, I'll go in front.
Nice, nice.
Nice jump.
Nice.
I'm charging the shield.
Run!
Here.
By the way, there are 6 teams left.
Oh!
I can do it!
I did it.
I made the knockdown shield stronger.
That's really nice.
Ouch!
He's on the second floor.
That hurts.
I really want to recover that.
No, if I had a little more time to spend
with you.
Nice jump
Hey!
That was strong.
Don't aim at the cute ones.
I'm at 0 damage.
No.
I was good at jumping.
I'm glad I could decide on my own.
I did it.
Let's have another 2nd round.
There's another chance.
I'm going to win.
I got a chance.
Trio? Duo?
Trio.
I got a chance.
Everyone, play the game.
Let's play a match with everyone.
But there are really a lot of one-chans.
I sometimes play a match with my
friends.
Wow, that's amazing.
Well, I don't have a lot of allies.
I play a match with my enemies.
There are a lot of them.
Wow.
If you play a match with them, you might
have a lot of allies.
I can still go.
What's the score?
The last 2,000.
Yes.
I'm going to get you.
Oh, I got the Octane.
I've already seen the future.
I can't use it except for Octane.
I'll be weak to the attack.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I thought it was red.
I'll introduce you to the new character.
If you pick it up.
Is it rare to use it except for Octane?
I don't use it at all.
I'd like to say that I'll close the suit
belt.
I'll protect you.
Leave it to me.
I'll protect Yunopy no matter what
character I use.
Leave it to me.
Don't worry, everyone.
I'll leave it to you.
I'll protect you even if I have to
become a wall.
I'm going to start APEX.
Please try it.
I think there are people who started
APEX because of the influence of ENO.
I think some people started watching
this live.
What? I can enter here.
I'll just take the scope first.
Oh, nice.
I'll take the repeater.
I didn't make anything here.
Oh!
I would you do
well derivative
Yeah Yeah Reiman.
Oscar
Dedications
I found a carbine.
Did you have it?
No, I didn't.
I'm glad.
I didn't have it.
I want a carbine of Yunope.
I don't have it.
That's not a carbine.
That's fake.
That's not it.
No
What should I do?
I want a nemesis.
I should go make one.
I wonder where I can make one near here.
Oh, I can go to the turbine.
I can make Nemesis there.
Can I go up there?
Yes, you can.
And you can go up there.
I'm glad I didn't run.
Oh, I see.
I did my best.
I found Sentinel.
I found my own.
She could be here from the walkthrough
that should work
Ok
Do you have a scope?
I have a scope
I'll put it on the flatline
Let's go down
It's not that good
I wonder if it's because I'm not good at
it
Oh, it wasn't for the scope
It wasn't for the scope
I found it
Nice
After I go there, I'll go down
Yes
I'll go to make armor
I'm weak with white armor
How do you go down?
Go back to the way you came
Jump from here
Go down
Yes, I did it
Nice
I got it
Thank you
Yeah, it's still fluffy.
I want to go to the garden.
It's going to be fun.
Octane is waiting for us.
Thank you, Octane.
Yes, yes.
A free person.
A free person?
There are quite a lot of free Octane
players.
You said you were a free person.
Yes, yes. There are quite a lot of free
players.
I think Ebe's character is really
unique.
I think she's a character that uses a
lot of things.
She's a kind Octane.
A kind Octane. Thank you.
Yes.
I'll make an armor here.
I got the materials.
And then,
I'll put the armor in the box.
Wait a minute.
I'm crafting.
Put it in.
And then, I'll put the armor in the box.
I see.
I got the materials.
And then, I'll make the accessories.
Okay.
I was hit.
Wait a minute.
It's not so far away.
It's close.
Be careful.
The enemy is shooting at us.
No, I'm a little...
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
I made a mistake on the way.
I think the line is cut off, so it's
okay.
But I don't know. The enemy is getting
closer.
I found another one.
I'm not a wife, so I'll go with him.
You're going to be revived
automatically, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
I always do it automatically, so I
forgot.
There he is! Let's hide.
Wait!
Stop it!
I hid for now.
You can go up.
I'm going to go up.
I know.
Oh, yeah!
I'm going to go down.
Okay.
It hurts, really.
I'm going to go down.
It's the right thing to do.
Get down.
Nice, run!
It's important not to get killed in this
game.
Even if you run, you win.
Yes, even if you run, you win.
They are fighting a lot.
Do your best and fight!
Enemy territory destroyed
Ah, it's pretty tray
Hmm..
the centre of the campaign
Thank you to embassy in the name of Sh防
Thank you for watching
just come
I should go
Dad
I'm sorry
Another, please
I'm not here so...
I ignored the enemy in front of me
There's a lot of enemies in front of you
I'm sitting down
There's an enemy in there so be careful
Let's go this way
I'll go around
By the way, we have a new ally
It's two of us
No, but don't worry
Don't worry and do it
I'm glad I didn't make an ally
So
I'll wake him up
He'll know where I am
I see
It's helpful if I'm here
It's also helpful if I'm not here
It's either way
I wonder if I should do this
What should I do?
Should I go to the safe zone?
Let's take a walk.
You're fast.
On the mountain...
I'll put the bottle here.
There's no meat.
I'll make some.
I'm going to make a meat.
Run! Run! Run! Go for it!
It's far away. I'm sure I can recover
this.
Let's recover the net!
Oh no! Oh no!
I can't make it! I can't make it! I
can't make it!
This is not good.
I can't make it! I can't make it!
I was defeated.
I'm going to save me and Neutron.
It's pretty anti-painful, isn't it?
Anti-painful.
It's painful.
No.
I'll wake up Lena.
I'll go to the third floor.
OK.
Nice. That's big.
The replicator is on the move.
I'll wake up Lena.
Thank you.
I think I've beaten you the most soberly
so far.
It happens sometimes.
Good luck, Lena.
I'll be back.
I want to go home, but I don't know how.
I want to toss the ball!
Yes, I can.
You not be able to do that.
I'm going to wake up.
Is there a time like this?
There is a time like this.
It's okay, everyone.
I'll wake up again.
He wasn't looking at that in this while
I do
Can Ka
I'll wake up Yunopy
I can wake Yunopy up
I can wake her up here
It's true
And there's a checkpoint so it's safe
even if she wakes up
Yunopy is back!
I'm back!
Yunopy is back everyone!
I'm alive again!
Thank you very much!
It's time to revive!
That's right!
Ah! Ah! Eh?
This is bad!
I'm going to sleep!
Eh! I'm sorry!
I was going to save you but I got
killed!
I'm coming to save you
Thank you!
I'm going to save you!
No, I can do it! I can do it! I can do
it!
I did it!
I just revived you!
I'm the revival YunaP!
Ah! The last one!
But, I'm still okay.
Everyone, I'm still okay.
There's one more.
Next time, for sure.
There's still more.
That's right.
This is the last one.
Let's open the New Picks box while we
wait.
Ah, I didn't wait.
Last one.
Last one. This is the last one.
This is the last one.
I want to finish with a champion.
Can I choose my wife?
First, there.
Please.
Can I use my wife?
Your wife.
Yes, please.
I'm happy to play games.
Let's play together.
I got it.
I made a mistake.
I'll go back.
I'm a third-person.
I'll go.
I'm going to introduce the champion this
time.
It looks strong.
Strong! Definitely strong!
This time, I'm the jump master.
I'll give you a present.
The way you say present is good.
Follow me. I'm the jump master.
I'll show you the power of the club I'll
show you I'll show you I'll do it
I want to get off safely
It's definitely safe
I can win with a 6-year-old
Bangalore-san Let's do our best together
Let's do it with Ban-chan
By the way, I'm wearing it
I'm wearing something
I was wearing a Zeratech.
What should I do?
I'm here.
I'm close to the enemy.
Run!
But...
I'm close to the enemy.
I was close to the enemy, so I ran away.
Nice decision.
I will do my best in the rampage.
By the way, I'm also in the rampage.
I'd like to go to the rampage.
I wonder if I should bring it to the
rampage.
Oh, it's strong if you get a termite.
I'll charge it.
It's
been approved so far.
Don't stop and wait
I want to try shooting, but even if I
get killed, I can recover now.
Where are the enemies?
It's strong. Can you break the window?
Rampart is opening the door.
Oh, 55!
It hurts!
Nice!
Come on!
Hey!
I'm running away!
Sorry, Shime!
Why are they shooting at me?
I got one shot.
They're shooting at me.
You don't have to be so hurt.
You are such a small and sad creature.
I didn't do that last one.
It was a practice.
That was...
Let's do it again.
This is the last one.
I didn't do it at all.
The last one of crying.
That's right.
I don't remember.
You don't remember, do you?
I don't.
I haven't done it yet.
Last one!
Yeah
What did you just do?
Oh, we can use our favorite characters
Alright, next one
Ah, nice
Nice
With this, if I get a Brachiosaurus, I
can get a Rover too
Oh, I got a Rover!
I'm happy
Nice
Nice, nice, nice trio
This is perfect, I'm going to win
See you later
Thank you
Ah, right, everyone remembers me eating
dumplings, right?
Right, right, right, I ate dumplings
I'm like a Lasso right now
Let samurai become a present
Could you get off
I have to chop
Eh ah ah ah
I see
I'm gonna do it.
There's an enemy over there.
Oh, it's a Spitfire.
I'm gonna do it.
Eh? You're not running away?
I'll throw something at you.
Eh? Eh? Eh? Wait, um...
Stop it already!
Wait, there's an enemy...
Let's go over there. I'm bored here.
I hit 18. Alright.
OK.
What are you doing?
I'm being watched.
It seems like your ally went to do it.
Good luck!
Oh, they're fighting.
Let's get along well.
Where did the enemy go?
There he is.
18!
Ouch! Where? I'm being shot from above.
Huh? I'm the only one left.
This is the last one.
I came to save my team, but I'm gone.
The enemy might be on top.
Let's move.
I thought I should move so I wouldn't
push my team.
Should I go this way?
I don't have any recovery items.
There are times like that.
There's a jump pad here.
I wonder what's over here.
I'd like to activate the safety.
Yes.
Hard mode.
I wonder if I should go around the shop
I wonder if I should go to the shop
Yes
The shop
I'll go around from here
Yes
Alright
I'll go around from here
I'll do my best
Yes, I'll do my best
.
Oh, by the way, I was doing Apex even if
I was alone the other day.
At that time, the enemy at that time was
a pretty kind person, and I was
able to get 1st place with a pretty kind
person.
I was waiting for me at the place where
I went a little while ago, and I was a
kind wife.
I was surprised because the person who
is really kind is really kind.
I was surprised that he threw me
recovery immediately after being hit
with various things.
I'm a pretty kind person.
It's fun to be a pretty kind person.
I think I'm getting good at pushing.
I threw away the Spitfire.
Is there anything you want?
I'm going to go get Nemesis.
Okay, Nemesis.
Let's go make something.
Okay.
I can't stop shaking.
Shake.
It stops when I hold my breath.
It's a bit of a shock.
It seems to stop when I hold my breath.
How is it?
I don't have to stop.
Wait, do you have a recovery?
I have a recovery.
I have a phoenix kit.
OK, OK, OK.
If there's a cell, I might as well go
around.
I'm in a safe position now.
Oh, but...
Oh, really.
Don't recharge the shield.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'll give you this.
Thank you.
Yes.
You're welcome.
I want a carbine, but I haven't seen it.
I haven't seen it. I'm looking for it.
I don't have a sleeping eye.
I can't wait any longer.
I found a carbine.
That's good.
I found a battery.
have all the
drilling.
Itakui
Kabuki I found an example too.
It's paper. Yunobi found all the armor
and the cover.
It was all in the same box.
It was all in one box.
I didn't expect that.
Wait, there's an enemy
Let's run
There's an enemy
There's an enemy!
I'm going to get shot
Oh no!
Is that all of them?
person Oh restrict not in the
much I was scrambled
Aso because have been going away
phenomenon over the back and lower
Look at this!
Yunopy is doing damage!
237 damage!
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing!
It's really amazing!
Look at this!
237 damage!
Look at this growth!
I'm impressed!
It was fun, so it's good!
If you can see the growth, it's okay!
Thank you very much!
So, that's it for today.
We ate gyoza and played games.
How was today's stream?
I learned how to beat enemies from
above.
I'll practice a little more and prepare
for the next stream.
How was it, Renomaru?
I'm so happy to have a cute Enopy.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
It was great to see the Mogumogu Yunope.
Yes.
So, please.
The next Stardust Gamers Club is
from 7 p.m. on September 15th,
at Hoshinami-Rie, Shiritsu-Eiwa,
Poppy Playtime.
It's this game.
It's really scary.
It's scary, isn't it?
If you run, your hands will stretch.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's really scary.
Please look forward to it.
Yes.
Can I announce it at the end?
Yes, please.
I'll go.
Yes.
On October 7th and 22nd,
the general release of the ticket for
OKARA DISCO 2023 will be held.
Yes.
It's a live with orchestra and dance
music as a concept,
so please come and see it.
Please.
Then I'll announce it, too.
Just now,
Hoshino-san from the same group.
Yes.
I heard it from the rumors of the wind.
I heard that your hobby is MOLK.
I heard that.
I'm currently on Stardust Web.
I'm playing MOLK on Stardust Web.
So,
I may appear in the MOLK tournament
soon.
Oh!
So, please check it out on Stardust Web.
I'm happy.
Yes.
Thank you.
So,
I hope you can call me again
as a member of this group.
I'll be gone for a month,
so I hope you can call me again.
I hope so.
Please leave your comments.
Yes.
Hashtag
Stardust Gamers Club.
Please.
I'm watching you.
Is it sad?
Yes.
I'll be gone.
Bye.
We just want to tell you that we are
wearing black clothes.
I want you to see this.
We just happen to wear this.
We are wearing this because we met
Yunopi.
We are wearing matching clothes.
We are wearing black one-piece.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
See you next time.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!